The Griselda Blanco Story
Cocaine Godmother is a drama, tv movie, crime
film directed by Guillermo Navarro.
At the age of 17, Griselda Blanco, made her way to the U.S.
with a fake passport with her first husband Carlos.
Living in Queens with her three sons, Griselda became enticed by the money the drug
world offered, and quickly became embroiled with local drug runners.
Griselda masterminded the use of beautiful women, the elderly and children as the mules
and created false-bottom suitcases to smuggle cocaine from Colombia.
Griselda Blanco, played by Catherine Zeta-Jones.
Darío Sepúlveda, played by Raúl Méndez.
Alberto Bravo, played by Juan Pablo Espinosa.
Carolina, played by Jenny Pellicer.
Dixon Trujillo Blanco, played by Matteo Stefan.
Osvaldo Trujillo Blanco, played by Spencer Borgeson.
Cocaine Godmother is a 2017 American biographical crime drama film
directed by Guillermo Navarro and written by David McKenna.
The film stars Catherine Zeta-Jones as Griselda Blanco,
who was known as the Cocaine Godmother.
It premiered at the 2017 Camerimage in Poland and showed
on Lifetime channel on January 20, 2018.
The tone is emotional.